<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programs on FRI Garage | Student technology accelerator</title>
    <link>https://garaza.io/en/programs/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programs on FRI Garage | Student technology accelerator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 12:50:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://garaza.io/en/programs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Programs</title>
      <link>https://garaza.io/programs</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garaza.io/programs</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student accelerator</title>
      <link>https://garaza.io/programs/accelerator</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 12:50:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garaza.io/programs/accelerator</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most important Garage activity. Selected student teams build their ideas in the accelerator programs.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have a great idea for a project? In the Garage, we will help to transform it from an idea to reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;workspace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mentoring for project (mentors from faculty or industry)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://garaza.io/faq/accelerator/microgrants&#34;&gt;microgrants&lt;/a&gt; (read: funds for the purchase of necessary equipment / services / software that you need for the project)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you apply your project:
- send the idea together with a description, timeframe and team members to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:garaza@fri.uni-lj.si&#34;&gt;our email&lt;/a&gt; or our personal emails in the Garage or on faculty
- if you are accepted in Garage, we specify the details together (finding a mentor, set the timing, resources, milestones of the project)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we expect:
- regularly working on the project (your team should meet and work at least once a week)
- visible progress of the project (for example: repository on Github)
- &lt;strong&gt;do not neglect your study commitments&lt;/strong&gt; while working on your project&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Milestones will therefore be set to adapt to your expected study obligations (eg. in a week, where there are many exams, you plan less activity on the project).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Under the hood&#34; workshops</title>
      <link>https://garaza.io/programs/workshops</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 12:50:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garaza.io/programs/workshops</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Practical (&amp;rdquo;&lt;em&gt;hands-on&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;) workshops on current technical topics.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In workshops &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Under the hood&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; we will together look under the hood and descend into the
details of the latest IT technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lecturers will be experts from industry, staff from faculty and of course, experienced students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;up to 15 participants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;made public in advanced:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agenda&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;duration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;difficulty level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;require prior knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;participants generally prefer to work on their computers, of course, there will be also computers in the Garage available to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming challenges and other competitions</title>
      <link>https://garaza.io/programs/programming-challenges</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 14:53:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garaza.io/programs/programming-challenges</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our faculty cooperates with different companies and works with them to prepare
our students a number of different challenges. All students, who participate in one of the challenges
can for the duration of the challenge use the premises of Garage for work.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Garage, we will also carry out several technical &lt;a href=&#34;https://garaza.io/programs/workshops/&#34;&gt;workshops&lt;/a&gt;, led by experts from industry who launch the challenge.
They are intended to be for both those who participate in the challenges as well as others who are only interested in the topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Programming challenges are published on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fri.uni-lj.si/si/raziskave/studentski_izzivi/&#34;&gt;a separate page&lt;/a&gt;,
where you can get more information about the challenge. Most of the programming challenges also have published all their material on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ucilnica.fri.uni-lj.si/course/index.php?categoryid=24&#34;&gt;Faculty classroom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group brainstorming and BoF sessions</title>
      <link>https://garaza.io/programs/bof-meetings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 12:50:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garaza.io/programs/bof-meetings</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brainstorming and BoF sessions are networking events with the aim to identify
ideas that are then used in the Garage or in a group to learn any new technology.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birds_of_a_feather_(computing)&#34;&gt;BoF sessions&lt;/a&gt;
and brainstorming are in comparison with the workshops &lt;a href=&#34;https://garaza.io/programs/workshops/&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Under the hood&lt;/em&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/a&gt;
more informal, non-structured activities and without a prepared detailed agenda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good ideas and interesting problems that are still looking for a team that would have &amp;ldquo;adopted&amp;rdquo;
them and park in the &lt;em&gt;Park of ideas&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>